Ana Chkhaidze: Okay, yeah. Okay.
Ana Chkhaidze: yeah. So what I 1st saw was just like, the longer I looked at the screen. It was just like a gradient of like black and red diagonally, so not like horizontally or vertically more diagonal, like at a 45 degree angle
Ana Chkhaidze: of just like the gradient of the gradient of black and red.
Ana Chkhaidze: And then, after that, I saw like
Ana Chkhaidze: everything in the screen, kind of just turned into like little stars of like red and black.
Ana Chkhaidze: Yeah, it was kind of like when you, when when you draw like little stars with
Ana Chkhaidze: the 4, the the 4 corners like the long stars instead of just like a 5 cornerstar.
Ana Chkhaidze: And then at 1 point, I saw would like seem to be like a figure. I don't know what the figure was. It was centered more towards the center of the screen.
Ana Chkhaidze: That's about it, like I couldn't tell who was supposed to be like a person or an object, but I'm assuming it was a person just because of it kind of looked like the neck shoulders that, and then up to the head.
Ana Chkhaidze: and then after that I saw 2 orgs
Ana Chkhaidze: and both of them were to were in like the bottom half of the screen, one to the left, the farthest left one to the farthest right, and then they kind of just like traveled up together into the middle of the screen, and then after that, once they like connected in the middle, they became one big orb, and then it went down the screen.
Ana Chkhaidze: and it was just like throughout the
Ana Chkhaidze: throughout the flashing I would just see like a lot of like stars
Ana Chkhaidze: going in and out and like the whole screen.
Ana Chkhaidze: And I think that was it.
Ana Chkhaidze: I'm done with the recording.
Ana Chkhaidze: I finished the recording. Oh, yeah, okay.